Hinasanpou 4th
Yay!
We're in Nagatoro today!
Dadaa!
Today...
My friends are here!
Come in.
Yay!
Hi, Hiyo-san's here.
Hello.
You know how sometimes I travel alone?
So I feel like I'm on a trip.
I'm going to have fun today.
Yay!
It's a nice atmosphere. It's calm.
It's a very calm and mature city.
I'm going to have fun.
Yay!
Oh, wow.
Ooh!
Wow!
I've never had a feature like this before.
So you've been with me almost every day for the last seven years or so.
I'm really quitting.
I'm quitting too.
Look at this! That's amazing!
There's something here.
It's here.
It looks like a festival.
There's miso fries.
It's famous.
Nibe-chan has been asking me to try them.
It's amazing.
Hello.
Can I have a bowl of miso fries, please?
Yes, I'll have one.
Looks delicious.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
Amazing. Looks so delicious.
Insert
Bon appétit.
It's the first time in my life.
Miso Potato
Hey!
Isn't the miso color really dark?
It sure is.
Is this what miso is?
Looks warm.
Looks hot.
Surprisingly good
Delicious
Sweet
And I've never seen them raw before
Miso Potatoes
It's so sweet and drunken and crispy.
Oh, yeah.
Delicious!
Bon appétit!
Like this.
You're a good eater.
Mmm-hmm.
Yum. Yum.
Delicious.
It's sweet and sour.
I'll have another one.
Yum.
Yeah, it's fun.
What do you think? It's kind of like her, isn't it?
Right around here, right?
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hm.
Hey. - Hey.
Oh, my God, right here.
Wanna go rafting?
Suddenly.
Do you want to go rafting?
We're going downstream.
It feels so good.
It feels like nature.
It's natural.
Much more natural.
Maybe it's a nice breeze.
The wind is right on.
It feels good.
I've never been on a river like this before.
I've never been to a river.
Okay, let's see Hina ride.
Hold on to me and start with your left foot.
Yes, sir.
Oh, it's really shaking a lot.
Thank you very much.
It shakes?
Yeah, it's fine.
Farther back.
Thank you.
Oh, wait, say that again.
Say it again.
Left foot first.
Yes!
Oh!
I got it!
I can do it!
It's gonna be fun.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
Cold wind.
Hey.
It's leaking so much.
Yay!
We're going to have a fast-flowing season, so look forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
The scenery is beautiful, so I can take lots of pictures.
Indeed.
Yes, like a lie.
Yes, I'll be careful.
I'll take pictures with this.
Take it, take it, take it.
Yoo-hoo, yoo-hoo.
Can I take any of them? Which one?
Oh, great. It's getting faster.
It's getting faster.
Wow, it's fast.
Hey.
I'm nervous.
There's a sheet behind your back to keep the waves off.
So please put it over your back so that you don't get wet.
Yes, sir!
If you're lucky, you'll get soaked!
Yo!
Is it that wet?
Oh, yeah, I got a little splashed.
Oh, my gosh!
It's easy to lose your ankles. - Oh, yeah?
Oh, yeah?
The waves are great.
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God.
Dive?
Dive.
This is it.
Oh, my God.
That was fun.
That's pretty close.
It's so close.
It's just a little too close.
What, you didn't get it?
It came so fast.
It's a little bumpy because we're going to skewer the boatman in the very front.
Yes, sir.
It's like a gusher.
Yes, sir!
We've arrived safely!
Thank you very much!
It's over. The line is down. It was fun.
Didn't it go by too fast? Did he say 15 minutes?
Fifteen minutes.
But don't you want to go back in the fall foliage? Come on, let's go.
Let's go?
I'd like to go with you.
I'll go with you.
Yay!
Ta-da! Here we are!
Ta-da!
You know what I mean?
See?
Rainbow trout, dark green.
I'm here to catch fish with my hands.
I can't imagine.
I can't. You've never done it before.
Look how cute the fish are!
It's true! Rainbow trout!
It's so cute.
That's nice. I'm excited.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's cold.
Oh, my God.
But, but, but...
Wait a minute... it's bigger than I thought.
Here it is.
Oh, my God.
It's huge.
Huge.
huge
Oh, wow, a sample.
It's a sample.
Grab the head
See?
Oh, wow.
Wow, that's great.
Good.
Oh, my God.
Let's try one of these.
If you put it in here.
Here you go.
Wow, that's cold.
Scary, scary, scary.
I'm cold.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Can you do it?
I think I'm a little scared.
What? I don't think I can film this.
Why not? It's scarier than I thought.
Are you gonna grab it? You're not gonna grab it, are you?
Go, go, go, go, go.
What the hell?
Wait a minute.
He's breathing through his gills.
Hey, gill breathing.
We breathe high.
I'll teach you.
We're breathing high.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. I think I can do that.
You're kidding.
Oh, I think I can do it. Hiyotan.
Oh, my gosh, that's amazing.
I'm scared.
Oh, wow.
That's great.
I got it.
Oh, my God! I got it!
Don't get together! Please!
I can do it, I can do it! Come on!
Almost there!
I touched it!
Oh, no! That was close!
I've never seen chicks like this before.
I'm okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Oh, no, I've rested!
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Touch it, touch it, touch it!
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Oh!
I got it.
Here are the little darlings we got.
Oh, dear.
The rainbow trout we just caught, I'm having them grilled now so I want to eat them. Wow!
I've never seen such a sight before.
Hot, hot, hot. It's amazing. It looks so delicious.
It's pretty hot even from this distance.
It looks delicious.
De-da-da-da-da-da.
Ta-da!
Mmm.
Smells like fish.
Hey...
Where do you eat it from?
I've never eaten it this way before.
I've never had it either.
Where do you eat it from?
That way.
That way? It's good.
Still that way.
It's expensive.
Yeah, it's good.
Mmm.
Very tasty!
Red.
Mmm. - Mmm.
It's good.
I like the salt.
Yeah, it's good.
Yum.
Thank you so much for the food.
It was fun.
It was really good.
It was so good.
It was so fluffy.
Ta-da!
I bought it!
I went to the supermarket in advance
and got the ingredients
I'd like to go to the barbecue now!
I've always wanted to barbecue!
And the river is amazing!
It's nice to be able to do it while being surrounded by nature!
Here we are!
Wow, wow, wow!
This is our barbecue spot today!
Wow!
It's so authentic.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know where to start.
Two people can barbecue.
That's for sure.
We can barbecue together.
What's today's love affair?
Orange juice.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Son melanin.
How about a quiz?
What are we going to make now?
Take a guess.
I got garlic.
Do you want to chop it?
Coarsely chopped.
Coarsely chopped?
What do you mean?
I don't care how you chop it.
Wow, doesn't garlic smell good?
Yes, it does.
It's coarsely chopped.
It's coarse-grained.
Oh, that's nice. Oh.
You want some more?
How much? A lot?
As full as you want it to be.
As much as you want?
It sounds good. It sounds like you're good. It sounds like you're good.
Do you want to put the garlic in first?
How much garlic do you put in first?
Do you put it in well?
Half a clove is good, right?
You want some food now?
Yeah, okay...
Aren't you guys good?
Very good. Perfect.
You'll be the best cook in the Kanazawa family.
I'm sure you will.
You'll be fine.
Oh, there's leftovers.
Do you put salt and pepper in it?
He said you can put a little.
He wrote it down.
I like salt and pepper.
Oh, it's kind of slimy.
Turns it up high.
Smells good salt and pepper.
Thank you.
Bird.
Okay, I get it. I think I'll add more sauce. What do you think?
Sure, I'll put it in.
Please do, doctor.
Maybe I'm lying again. What do you think?
I don't know.
Maybe we should let the doctor decide.
You want a taste?
Sure.
I'll give it a once-over.
Oh, I'll check.
There's been a lot of cat food lately.
I've had this baked cat's tongue before.
I heard you can eat it even if it's hot if you don't put it on the tip of your tongue.
If you don't put it on the tip of your tongue?
That's right.
It comes right out the back.
You can't taste it.
Yeah. - Yeah.
It's so garlicky.
It's so good.
That's amazing!
It's done.
I didn't tell you the right answer, did I?
Oh, yeah.
The correct answer is Pepper Lunch.
I'm going to eat a lot of garlic.
Yes.
Ta-da!
How is it?
Is it good?
Meat and garlic.
It tastes good. It's invigorating.
A little thicker.
How's it taste?
It's fine.
I think I'm gonna be satisfied.
Yeah.
It's not like barbecue.
I'm gonna smoke this one out and make something else.
What do you want?
What do you like?
But Hiyori and his friends don't really talk when they go out for yakiniku.
They don't talk.
We don't talk at all. We don't talk at all.
Maybe when we're ordering.
Or when we're deciding what to do.
Bon appétit!
Bon appétit.
Crunchy.
Sorry. Sorry.
Yutan, I might have taken the tastier one.
No problem.
Here we are. Here we are.
Put it on like this. Put it on like this.
Go, go, go, go!
I'm scared.
It's right. It's right. It's right.
It fits. It fits.
Great, great, great, great.
It's burning, it's burning, it's burning.
The chimney.
Wow, wow, wow. Isn't that intense?
Bon appétit.
Can I eat this right now?
It'll warm you up.
Yeah, it's good.
Marshmallow.
Just marshmallows?
Just marshmallows.
But don't you remember the campfire?
We did it in the bonus video, right?
We did.
Well, each one of us had our own choreography.
Remember when we played cards together during recess, breaks, and standby?
We did! I remember so much. It was hard.
Weren't you still in high school or something? Not at all.
That's about the same time.
You were together almost every day for the past 7 years.
You mean you spent 6 years of elementary school together?
Yeah, more than that.
First grade?
Second grade?
Ninth grade.
Wow!
Isn't it weird?
Doesn't it feel like we've been together for a while?
A couple of years.
Long time.
A couple of years. Oh, man.
Short.
Two or three years is short.
But I remember so much...
I think...
I wanted to go to a hospital for self-loading or something, you know, like a hospital, right?
But Hiyotan didn't know anything, so at first he couldn't see the train or the map.
So I think I asked Hina to go with me.
We had a lot of sleepovers during that period.
And Hiyotan's plates were pink and light blue, and we used to eat curry on them.
Dishes that made me lose my appetite.
And the night meal?
I used to eat at night, you know.
When he eats around 10:00 p.m.
Piyotan had rice cakes.
Sent from his parents' house.
He ate a lot of rice cakes.
He ate so much rice cakes that they were all he had to eat.
But we actually had a fight once.
No one knows about that?
No, I don't think so.
I don't know what the fight was about.
I had to pretend to remember it right away.
The next day.
A singing show?
A singing show.
And
What's everyone's opinion?
We'll talk about it together.
You know, like, "Go watch the video and memorize it.
Almost all of them
I don't have a lot of time to teach.
I was the type of person who wanted to do the best I could on my own.
I was the type of person who wanted to do it on our own.
After watching the video
Rihiyo-tan is
someone who knows how to do it.
If someone knows the moves, let's ask them to teach us.
I was like, "Let's learn it.
I don't know all the details.
So I thought it would be faster to have someone teach me.
But Hina should watch the videos.
Like, let's do it on our own.
Yeah, but neither of them are bad.
No, it's not that bad. They both have their own opinions.
Yeah, we argued a lot.
Like, "No, but, you know...
I think we're both
I don't really have a lot of time to spare. No, no, no, but...
It was at night, so it was like, wouldn't it be better if I learned it myself now?
We argued, and things got a little tense.
We both kind of fell silent.
And then you tried not to cry for a second.
Like, "We just had a fight, didn't we?
I said, "Sorry, I thought we just had a fight.
It was just a moment. That's all I could think of.
We don't fight.
It's growing. Suddenly.
I'm sorry. That's great. That's great.
Wait, you did it. You did it like this.
You can do it so well.
I interrupted you in the middle of a conversation.
This is a new discovery. It'll grow even more.
I'm going to try it to the max.
I'm sure it's going to grow a lot.
You can't eat this by yourself.
You're going to have to eat it.
I have to have this.
What's that?
This is late September, right?
October, November.
Fukuoka is in November.
November.
No.
It's the first of December.
No. 4.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Number four.
Graduation.
It doesn't fly by, does it?
Three months already?
Not three months.
It's almost October.
It's October.
November, December.
Two months.
Oh, man.
Two months can really pass in three seconds, I swear.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Two more months and I'm gone.
Two months.
Do you feel it?
Really?
But it's true, I've been feeling it a lot lately.
You know, when people say goodbye to me, you know, fans.
I've had people talk about it in their letters and messages, so...
That I'm really quitting.
That's true.
But I really think...
Even if he quits, he's definitely going to stay with Hinen, right?
He moved out of here.
He'll definitely tell her.
Like, "I'm going to this supermarket now.
I'll definitely tell him.
Right?
Even today, it all happened so fast.
Today went by so fast.
It's so cold.
I think I'll get a heart.
These clothes, too...
There's a brand of jerseys like this.
No? Jersey brand?
Sports broads, like this one.
It was a really nice day. I'm the type of person who stays at home.
It's true, you can make the day last longer if you go outside.
You're right, it's obvious.
But it's important.
This kind of calm, natural place is the best for you.
Everyone is so kind.
So, thank you all for watching.
It's your birthday near here, isn't it?
You? Me? Who are you talking about? That's right, it's my birthday.
I'd like to celebrate your birthday with everyone today.
Happy Birthday to you Happy Birthday to you
Happy Birthday to you!
The cake is here!
It's really here!
It's here!
It's out!
What? When did it come?
I'm 22 years old. Thank you very much, I turned 22.
I'm 22 years old now.
My ambition is to win the first prize.
But, you know, that was before you turned 22, too.
This goal since I was 20 years old.
I'm just saying that I haven't achieved it yet.
Keep up the good work!